哈喽 你能不能帮我找一下
Hello. Um, I was wondering if you could help me
今早来的杂志
find a magazine that was due in this morning.
叫做风骚女子
It's called "Minx."
-是俄语吗  -不 那叫明斯克
- Is that Russian? - No, that would be Minsk.
风骚女子是荡妇的美化称呼
No, "Minx" is a clever play on the word "floozy."
讽刺的是那个杂志是主张女性主义的
It's ironic 'cause the magazine is feminist.
比如时尚杂志吗 在货架上呢
Like "Cosmo"? That's on the rack.
不在
Uh, nope.
那个杂志吧 有点色情的
Uh, it has a more e-erotic bent.
你看是这几本吗
Did you check here?
我看了 不在那里
I did. It's not-- it's not there.
哦 是那个露屌的吗
Oh, the one with the dick in it.
达瑞斯 那个露屌的杂志你上货了吗
Hey, Darius! Did you stock that new mag with the dick in it?
在收银台下面 傻逼
Check under the counter, doofus!
不对 不是这本
Nope. No. Not that one.
找到了
Oh, yeah, here it is.
当个收银员都有职业风险
Talk about an unsafe job site.
好的
That's great.
天啊 谢谢你
Oh, my God. Thank you so much.
玩去吧
Have fun.
玛丽做了个子宫切除术（谐音:歇斯底里）
最近的销售额
So sales so far have not been-
确实不理想 但是我也见过更糟糕的
they-- they've just not been ideal, but I've seen worse.
-是吗  -是的
- You have? - I have.
也见过更好的 绝对有更好的销售额
And better. Definitely better.
这一点也不惊讶
Look, this is not surprising, okay?
没有女人会想去买那种
No woman wants to buy a magazine
让自己感觉是个猥琐女的杂志
if she's made to feel like a pervert.
我们必须想办法
We have to think of a way
让它不要被遗弃在收银台下面
of getting it out from under the counter.
没错 我们必须引起人们的意识
That's right. We-- we need to create awareness.
得有人谈论这杂志 问有没有卖的
We got to get people talking about it, asking about it.
-没错  -真的有人读吗
- That's right. - Is anyone reading it?
-当然有了  -那就好
- Of course they are. Yes. - Okay.
在格林威治村
We're big in, uhm Greenwich Village...
普罗文斯镇
uh, Provincetown...
卡斯特罗卖的都很好
the Castro.
-在卡斯特罗卖得好  -有趣
- We're big in the Castro. - Intriguing.
这股势头需要建立
So let's build off that momentum.
让我们的第二期成为爆款
Let's make issue two a knockout.
要不我们做明星采访也行啊
What about a celebrity interview?
-确实  -不错
- Ooh, yeah. - Good. Yeah.
贝拉·艾布札格 肯定有故事要说
Ooh, Bella Abzug-- I bet she has some stories to tell.
Bella Abzug 前美国众议院议员
-性感的故事吗  -也许吧
- Sexy stories? - Maybe.
-我差点就请到杰奎琳了  -泰迪还是鲍比
- I'm one degree from Jackie O. - Bobby or Teddy?
-没错  -我们需要采访
- Yes. - I-I think we need somebody
有爆点的明星
with a little bit more sizzle, right?
大明星
A bigger name.
我来给个建议哈
How about-- I'm just gonna throw this out there,
比利·布伦森如何
but what about Billy Brunson?
-那是谁啊  -好吧
- Who? Who's that? - Okay.
比利·布伦森 山羊队的比利·布伦森
Billy Brunson, the Goat. Billy Brunson.
打了沃伦·比蒂一拳的橄榄球运动员
The football player who punched out Warren Beatty.
不要 我的天啊 绝对不哟
No. No! G-God, no, absolutely not.
采访人物必须和我们杂志的目标一致
No. They have to align with the mission of the magazine,
无论他们有多出名
no matter how famous.
他挺有名的 我觉得我们需要运用比尔的
Oh, he's pretty famous. I think we should use Bill--
道格 有快递
Doug, delivery.
你给我签收了呗
Okay, well, you can sign for it.
我签收不了
Uh, no, I can't.
这是怎么回事 他们拒收了两万五千本杂志吗
Hey, what's going on? They sent back 25,000?
说是内容不堪入目
Something about indecent material.
这帮混蛋 都不事先跟我说一声
Tempe desert rats-- not even a heads-up.
我还能咋说呢老兄
I don't know what to tell you, man.
他们打过几次
They called a few times.
加里·布雷克纳 运营副总裁
Gary Breckner, VP of Operations.
-你都没回电话  -我以为我们欠他们钱呢
- You never returned. - I thought we owed them money.
-我们确实欠他们钱  -看吧 我说的没错
- We do owe them money. - Well, you see? I was right.
快点给我签收
Somebody needs to sign for these.
我跟你说罗恩
I'll tell you what, Ron--
不管节俭超市付你多少钱 我都会出双倍
whatever Thrifty's paying you, I'm gonna double it.
你能不能在我搞清楚之前 在这儿待会儿
Will you just stick around until I figure this out?
很好 太棒了
Oh, great. Very good.
道格
Doug...
这些杂志不能算在我们头上
we cannot eat these magazines.
你觉得我不知道吗 蒂娜
You think I don't know that, Tina?
我们没钱出这个费用
We don't have the cash to cover the cost.
不光是节俭超市
It's not just Thrifty.
-啥意思  -小猪扭扭超市的也打电话来了
- What are you talking about? - Piggly Wiggly called.
操 操 操 操
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
好吧
Okay.
操
Fuck!
好了
Okay!
有意思的部分来了 我们的产品很好
This is the fun part. We got a good product.
现在我们只需要告诉人们这款产品
Now we just got to tell people about it.
我们现在只需要这么办
That's all we got to do right now.
好啊 我手上有很多大媒体的联系方式
All right, well, I have some pretty big media contacts,
我觉得肯定会有人帮忙找个大人物
and I bet one of them can help land a big fish
用来做封面
for the front cover--
让人强烈兴奋的女性主义者
you know, a feminist with frisson.
这才对嘛 乔伊斯
See, that's what I'm talking about, Joyce!
-看到没 太棒了 快点行动吧  -好的
- See? Good! Hustle! - Okay.
你觉得咱们是怎么成立的
How do you think we built this place?
这地方就是逼出来的
We built this place with hustle!
蒂娜 快过来
Tina, come here, please.
我和蒂娜 开着车到处给大家
Me and Tina driving around, handing out "Lusty Lesbos"
派发《淫荡百合》
to anybody who would take it,
结果之后大家都想要了
and the next thing you know, people were begging for it.
风骚女子这么做也能成
And they're gonna do that with "Minx."
我还是比较了解
Well, I know a thing or two about our intended audience,
我们的目标受众的
and I will tell you this.
他们是由恐惧驱动的
They're motivated by fear,
担心别人有他没有的东西
fear of someone having something they don't.
你住的地方是不是挺高大上的
You live someplace hoity-toity, right?
-你很有钱  -没错 衣食无忧吧
- You're rich. - Yeah, we're comfortable.
很好我为你感到高兴 你现在要做的是
I'm happy for you. Good. Here's what I want you to do.
你带着斑比
I want you to take Bambi.
车上装满杂志
I want you to fill your car up with magazines.
全都免费派送
I want you to give them away, all of them, for free.
-好的  -好的 相信我
- Okay. - Good. Yes. Trust me.
我知道有个地方可以去
I have an idea where I can go.
很好 这就对了
Good. That's what I'm talking about!
很好 有能动力 很棒
Great! Good initiative! Good stuff!
我们就是要赢
This is what we're gonna do! We're gonna win...
-好的  -就这个团队
- Okay. - As this team.
很好 我们就是顶尖团队
Good! The A-team!
你要怎么办
What are you gonna do?
我要坐下一班航班去亚利桑那州坦佩
I'm gonna catch the next flight to, uh, Tempe, Arizona,
我们必须让我们的杂志重新上架节俭超市
and I'm gonna get our magazines back on the Thrifty shelves.
嗨 格伦
Oh, Glenn.
-乔伊斯  -你好
- Joyce. - Hello.
你怎么来了啊
Hey. What-- what are you doing here?
我就在附近
I was in the neighborhood,
我们还没有一起吃过午餐 所以
and we never got that lunch, so...
我知道 我给你发消息了来着
No. I know. I-I left you a few messages. I just--
我知道 抱歉 我太忙了
I know. I'm sorry, it's been crazy.
我给你买了点费南雪蛋糕
But, um, anyway, I got some financiers
从那个在伯顿你喜欢的面包房买的
from that bakery we like on Burton.
-哦  -我就想来看看你
Oh. Figured I'd say hi.
太棒啦 谢谢你
That's so sweet. Thank you.
你想打开尝尝吗
Um, you want to crack them open?
好的
Yes, I do.
你是要在这附近开会吗 还是什么的
So, what, do you have a meeting nearby or...?
没错
I do. Yeah.
我得给第二期找个亮眼的名字
I've got to get a big splashy name for issue two.
简·方达 我的公关说
So-- oh, Jane Fonda's, uh, publicist
她可能会感兴趣
says that she might be interested, so...
那还挺不错的啊
Wow. That'd be a big get.
确实
Yeah, it would. You know what?
不过她总是搪塞我
I'm getting the runaround, though.
我还没有跟她联系那么紧密
I don't quite have the contacts yet.
这种东西得需要几年时间来培养
Yeah. Well, those can take years to cultivate.
-你还有什么想法  -天啊
- Who else you thinking? - Oh, God.
我不想用我乏味的工作困境来烦你
No, I don't want to bore you with my tedious work dilemmas.
别这样 我乐意至极
Stop, please. It's my pleasure.
这是一些原始的点子
Some first ideas.
苏珊·桑塔格肯定会拒绝
Okay. Susan Sontag, she'll say no.
维多利亚·哈特内特
Victoria Hartnett.
-我喜欢她  -我知道
- I love her. - I know you do.
但是她只会上那些著名的杂志 比如纽约客
But she only does fancy stuff-- "The New Yorker."
我有主意了
I have an idea.
温迪·马
Wendy Mah.
那个暴力性爱的温迪·马吗
- "Aphrodisia" Wendy Mah? - Yeah.
我本来想为我们这个月的杂志采访她
I was supposed to interview her for Crush of the Month,
但是想要在交稿之前交来不及了
but we just couldn't make it work by deadline.
别了吧 她的书就是一些装模作样的庸俗口号
I don't know. Her book, it's middle-brow pablum
还要装作是关于性赋权的论文
posing as a treatise on sexual empowerment.
-你读过吗  -当然没有了
- You read it? - No, of course not.
《被时代杂志》批的很厉害
"The Times" eviscerated it, though.
-你读过吗  -是的
- Did you? - I did.
为了工作 我必须看
Well, I had to for work.
但是我觉得吧
But I don't know.
还挺有意思
I found it entertaining...
也很撩人
And provocative.
它流行不代表是不好的啊
Just because something is popular doesn't mean it's bad.
不过它确实把《海鸥乔纳森》
I mean, she did knock "Jonathan Livingston Seagull"
踢出了畅销书排行
off the best-seller list.
她在伍德布里奇教书呢
You know, she's teaching right over at Woodbridge.
我能给你安排一场见面
Bet I could get you a meeting.
那我算是来对了
Then I guess I came to the right place.
纽约伯班克机场
别说什么盖世太保战术
Okay, but don't say the thing about Gestapo tactics.
-让人听起来怪怪的  -但是事实就是如此
- It sets the wrong tone. - But that's what this is.
加里·布雷克纳凭什么决定节俭超市的客户
I mean, who is Gary Breckner to decide what is decent
应该看什么杂志啊
for Thrifty customers?
运营副总裁有权这么做
Vice President of Operations who has the right to do that.
-他连花花公子都卖  -好吧
- He sells "Playboy." - Okay.
你觉得没勃起的鸡巴
Are you saying that soft dick
比浓密阴毛更让人反感吗
is more offensive than a hairy bush?
浓密阴毛不是女性的性器官
A hairy bush is not the female sex organ.
-不都是阴道吗  -听我说
- It's all vagina. - Okay, listen.
人家允许我们见一面就已经很不错了好吧
You are lucky we even got a meeting, okay?
那些杂志在货车上呆的越久
The longer those magazines stay on that truck,
我们就越完蛋了
the more fucked we are,
能不能振作起来 解决此事
so just please pull it together and make this right.
好的 我同意
Okay. I agree.
好的
Okay.
交给我吧
I got this, okay?
下班前我会回来的
I will be home by happy hour.
我来机场接你哈
Okay. I'll be back to get you.
-很好  -旅途愉快
- Great. - Have a safe flight.
谢谢你
Thank you.
借过下
Excuse me.
布雷克纳先生听到我说的话之后
And I think once Mr. Breckner hears what I have to say--
那你能不能告诉他
Well, would-- would you please tell him that he--
他今天必须找出时间见我
he has to make time for me today
因为我现在就在飞机上
'cause I'm at the airport right now.
已经要登机了
I'm about to board.
我一个半小时就到
I'll be there in an hour and a half.
就不能跟我见一下吗
I think what I'm asking for is just a little face time.
那运营副总裁上面的人是谁
Well, then who's above the Vice President of Operations?
我不知道他的老板是谁 我不是这家公司的员工
I don't know who his boss is. I don't work for the company.
布雷克纳先生
Hi, Mrs. Breckner?
好 卡萝尔 你还好吗
Oh, good. Hey, Carol, how are you?
我想问问你家在哪
Say, I was wondering, what's your home address?
你能这么快就见我
Look, I really appreciate
我非常感激
you meeting us on such short notice.
可惜我们没能让这玩意计件工作
Well, I felt bad we couldn't make the "Lad" piece work.
哇偶 帅哥啊
Awoogah. Hey, big fella.
是啊
Yeah.
童养媳
Child brides, ugh.
14岁就做爱已经够惨了
It's one thing to screw at 14,
你能想象还要结婚吗
but can you imagine being married?
-真是噩梦  -确实是噩梦
- Nightmare. - It is a nightmare.
在孟加拉
In Bangladesh, there's-- - Uh, you know,
对了 乔伊斯对暴力性爱很感兴趣 温迪
Joyce really responded to "Aphorodisia," Wendy.
对 没错 你知道吗
Yeah. God, oh, yes. Yeah. You know what?
你的色情文学作品中的那种燃情
You have a flare for literary erotica
而不媚俗
without ever devolving into the profane.
这话真该让《巴黎评论》的那帮太监听听
Tell that to the eunuchs at "The Paris Review."
或者 或者可以为你写篇长专题
Or you could. You could write a whole feature.
听着不错
That sounds fun,
但应付采访和教书不能两全
but between press and my course load--
这都不是事儿 我们会想办法
Uh, we'd figure out a way to make it work
迎合你的时间表的
with your schedule.
-我可以等你上完课再过来  -好的 要么就
- I can come back after class. - Sure. Maybe...
不行 女权主义者集体会议
No, feminist collective meeting.
我是教师顾问
I'm faculty advisor--
应该说 教师姐妹
sorry, faculty sister.
当年在瓦萨学院 乔伊斯当过女权集体的领导
You know Joyce ran the feminist collective at Vassar.
“冥界女神崛起” 没有正式领导结构
Persephone Rising had no formal leadership structure,
不过我确实主持过几场会议
but I did facilitate most of the meetings.
是吗 那一起来吧
Really? Come by.
我们一直在找特邀演讲者
We're always on the hunt for guest speakers.
天啊 我何德何能
Oh, gosh. I'm not sure I'm accomplished enough
不敢当不敢当
to, you know, warrant that honor.
你可是出版界的女精英
You're a successful woman in publishing.
大家会对你趋之若鹜的
They'll eat you right up.
所以 会后我们可以
So-- so then afterwards,
讨论下你和《风骚女子》么
we could talk about you and "Minx"?
-到时候见咯  -好的
- I'll see you there. - Okay.
-太棒了  -干得好
- Yes! - Good job.
是你干得好
You did a good job.
谢谢你
- Thank you. - That was awes--
嗯 你今天下午有啥安排吗
Okay, hey, have you got any plans for this afternoon?
没什么急事
No. Nothing that I have to rush back for.
你有什么建议
What'd you have in mind?
太好了 咱们去搞搞草根营销
Okay, great. Just a little grassroots marketing.
开路吧
Lead the way.
-搞什么  -抱歉啊
- Hey! - I'm sorry.
不好意思 我们看得太入迷了
Oh, yeah. We were just so distracted.
你们在看啥
What's that?
天哪 是根雕儿吗
Oh, my gosh. It's a kick.
姐妹之前没看过《风骚女子》么
You've never heard of "Minx" before?
-这杂志都被吹爆了  -是吗
- Everyone's talking about it. - They are?
到处都断货
Yeah. Too bad it's sold out everywhere.
-可惜了  -这样呗
- Oh. - You know what?
我这本送你了
Here, why don't you take my copy?
-贝琪  -没事的 简
- Becky! - It's okay, Jane.
我们已经亨用过了
We've already had our fun.
-谢谢  -好好享受
- Thanks. - Enjoy!
走吧
Okay, um...
开甲壳虫的 都是一群神秘怪胎
Volkswagen Beetle. They're always secret freaks.
我就开这车啊
That's what I drive.
谢谢
Thank you.
-最近怎么样  -很不错
- How's it going? - I'm good.
小费给你
Here you go.
等等
Um, actually,
不如把你的杂志给我一本如何
how about you give me one those magazines instead?
没问题 布鲁诺 阅读愉快
All right. Enjoy, Bruno.
谢啦
Thank you.
别告诉我 我错过派对了
Don't tell me I missed the party.
抱歉 卖光了
Oh, sorry, fresh out.
存货都没了 还算什么推销员
What kind of salesman doesn't bring enough product?
我可不是推销员 我是摄影师
Not a salesman. I'm, uh, the photographer.
你拿相机了吗
You got a camera on you?
布里特 卡姆 布洛克 你们负责女生联谊会
All right, Brit, Cam, Brock, you're hittin' sorority row.
切特 巴克 丁格斯 去教育系
And, Chet, Buck, Dingus, education.
要是遇到阻碍 就去啦啦队那边试试
And if you strike out there, try cheerleading practice.
或者呢
Alternatively,
政治学专业今年的女生特别多
poli-sci is flush with female majors this year.
真棒
Wonderful.
顺便也去历史系和经济管理系碰碰运气
May as well run by history and econ as well.
赶紧着 大家动起来
Move, maggots! Let's go! Hidey-ho!
等着我踢你们屁股呢
Don't make be bring out the spoon!
这是啥梗
The what?
一入兄弟会 终生兄弟会
Once a Beta always a Beta.
你召集人力的效率
Well, the efficiency of the manpower
让我叹为观止
you have summoned is undeniable,
但一帮兄弟会的人真的适合
but are fraternity brothers the right--
叫传承者 虽然他们还没正式获封
Pledges. They haven't earned it yet.
抱歉 但让一帮 “传承者”
Oh, I'm sorry. Are pledges the right emissaries
去宣传《风骚女子》真的合适吗
to be spreading the "Minx" message?
别想太多 好吗
Listen, don't overthink it, okay?
大家正热火朝天地帮你的杂志造势
We are actively getting your magazine out there right now.
自己看
Look at it.
你不想沦为那人一样的下场吧
I mean, you don't want to end up like that guy, do you?
伍德布里奇学院剧场《蓬岛仙舞》本周上演
男高音 男高音
Tenor? Tenor? Tenor?
不想 我对你感激不尽
No, really. I cannot thank you enough.
我们有机会约到了温迪
You know, we have a real chance of booking Wendy.
我还可以跟我创办《风骚女子》
And I get to talk to the women
的读者面对面的交谈
that I actually made "Minx" for.
甚至还能培养一些好苗子出来
I might even come out of this with some mentees.
这就对了
There you go.
丁格斯 你在干吗呢
Dingus, what are you doing?
动起来 丁格斯 加油
Come on, Dingus. Move it!
没错
Yeah.
真没想到她谈起亡夫
I did not expect her
嘴下那么不留情
to talk about her dead husband that way.
这就像一场盛大的犹太成年礼
We're really doing a mitzvah here.
我是1/18的德裔犹太人好吧
I'm 1/18 Ashkenazi.
我们还剩几箱
How many boxes do we have left?
-应该只剩两箱  -好的
- Um, just two, I think. - Okay.
对了 我家孩子学校旁边的那家吉根森
Oh, the Jurgensen's by my kid's school!
那些家长协会的妈妈会爱死的
Those PTA moms will love it.
耶
Yeah.
太美了
Beautiful.
你的朋友都是模特儿吗 还是说只有丹和本吉
All your friends models or just Dan and Benjy over here?
模特 演员 白马王子
Models, actors, escorts...
只要钱到位 什么姿势都会
whatever pays the bills. - Hmm.
大家谋生的手段真是丰富多彩哈
We all do very different things to pay the bills.
今天你走运了
Well, today's your lucky day
让你体验一把过节的感觉
because you're the one about to get paid.
我在生命中走了一段弯路
♪ But I ran into a detour in my life ♪
天啊
Oh, wow.
这地方真不错
Oh, this place. - Mm-hmm.
要知道 我的小伙伴当年都在地下室会面
God, my collective met in the basement
楼里还散发着一股甲醛味道
of a science building reeking of formaldehyde.
那你可能会跟这个东西有共鸣
Then this piece might speak to you.
是吗
Oh, okay.
这是羊子宫
- That's a sheep's uterus. - Oh.
“玛丽做了子宫切除术”
"Mary Had a Little Hysterectomy."
你知道吗 一旦女人有了资源
You know, it's just- it's amazing
她们做出的成绩往往令人拍案称奇
what women can create when they have the resources, you know?
你看这里
I mean, look at this.
连这些日常小细节也打理得很美
This-- even the quotidian is so beautiful.
这个颜色如此深沉
Such depth of color here.
这是月经血蜡染而成的
Those are menstrual drippings.
姐妹们 下午好
Sisters, good afternoon.
我们今天要迎来一位特殊来客
As you know, we have a very special guest today.
我知道你们中有人已经
I see some of you have formed a relationship
爱上了她的作品
with her material already.
大家用姐妹团结会的方式热烈欢迎
How about a warm Sisters of Solidarity welcome
乔伊斯·普里格尔的到来
for Joyce Prigger?
我是站着 还是坐
Do I-- um, do I-- uh, do I stand here or--
这里没有等级制度
There are no hierarchies here.
好的 那我就坐你们中间
All right. Should I just absorb in?
-坐那就好  -好 让我先 好的
- Just tuck right in there. - I'm just-- yeah. All right.
好
So all right.
好了
Okay.
可以了
好不容易穿回裙子
The one time I decide to wear a skirt.
看来你已经舒舒服服坐好了
Looks like you're nice and comfy.
对
Yes.
我还得去办几件事
So I've got a few errands to run.
-你们会聊得很开心的  -你不留下么
- You're gonna get along great. - Uh, you-- you're not staying?
我都是昨日黄花了 对吧女士们
Oh, I'm yesterday's news, right, ladies?
拜拜
Ciao!
-嗨  -我想提个意见
- Hi. - I have a contribution.
这个雕儿太疲软
This penis is flaccid.
好像在说女生太温顺 不敢直面男生勃起
I resent the implication that women are too meek
这种暗示让我很不适
to confront an erect phallus. all: Mm-hmm.
开门见山 好嘞
Diving right in, I see. All right.
其他人也这么觉得吗
Um, does anybody else feel that way?
冰箱里有个墨西哥玉米卷
There's a taco casserole in the freezer,
放烤箱里热一下就行
so just pop it in the oven.
对 我马上就回家
Yeah. I'll be home in a jiff.
350度
45分钟
45 minutes.
锡箔纸别撕
Keep the foil on.
不是让你吃进去 撕下来
No, not to eat it. Take it off for that.
爱你
Love you.
我热之前一般喜欢
I like to bring mine to room temp
先解冻一下
before I pop it in the oven.
那肯定 前提是他得有时间
Well, obviously, if he had the time.
好的
All right.
谢谢你
- Thank you. - Mm-hmm.
咱就是说 谁能想到在学校1000英尺内
I mean, who knew it was illegal to hand out pornography
散播色情作品还违法啊
within 1,000 feet of a school?
不过这话一出口 确实感觉不妥
Now that I say it out loud, it does make a lot of sense.
麦克尼尔警官说这是新规定
Officer McNeal said it was a new ordinance,
我们是第一例违反规定的女人
and we're the first women to violate it.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你人这么好 这么守规矩
You're so nice and normal.
可你的邻居和那些家长会妈妈们
It's your community and all those snooty moms
差点看到你被铐走
almost saw you get cuffed.
老天啊
Jesus!
没事的
It's-- it's fine.
你今后还怎么去超市买东西
Where are you gonna get groceries?
那个助理经理似乎
I mean, that assistant manager
下定决心要给你开出终身禁令
seemed very serious about your lifetime ban.
好吧 我去别的地方买就是了
Yeah. So I'll-- I'll shop someplace else.
你怎么这么冷静
Why are you being so cool about this?
说实话 我都不记得
Honestly, I-I can't even remember
自己上次闯祸是什么时候了
the last time that I got in trouble.
感觉竟然有点刺激
And it felt kind of good.
你的意见我听到了 萨布里纳
I receive your contribution, Sabrina,
但《风骚女子》的目标之一
but one of the goals of "Minx"
是揭示所有
is to reveal the oppressive nature
传统关系中的压迫本质
of all traditional relationships.
所以我们女同关系
So now my lesbian relationship
就不存在传统和压迫一说么
can't be traditional or oppressive?
你真的想吗
Do you want it to be?
为什么没有工薪阶层女性的故事
Where are the stories about working-class women?
或者非白人女性故事
Or women who aren't white?
或是原住民社区的强迫节育
Or forced sterilization of indigenous communities?
大家想法都很棒
Good ideas, all,
但我们每期只能发这么多文章
but we can only have so many articles per issue
否则会超出广告售额
based on the ads that we can sell.
原来你们的内容掌握在
So the monsters of Madison Avenue
麦迪逊大道那群怪物手里
dictate your content?
纽约麦迪逊大道 多家知名广告公司总部所在地
我倒希望是麦迪逊大道
Oh, God. I wish it was Madison Avenue.
更像是文图拉马路吧
It's more like, uh, Ventura Boulevard.
我看出来了 你在乎的是利润
Clearly, profits are more important to you
而不是自由
than liberation.
我知道 这本杂志
I understand that this magazine
不能让所有人满意
can't please everyone,
但我们在很多重要问题上 已经引起了关注
but we are bringing attention to important issues,
那些你们提过多次的问题
issues that you have raised many times--
上沃尔特共和国的阴蒂切除术 婚内强奸
clitoridectomy in Upper Volta, marital rape.
本来是有希望的 但你止步于此
That had promise, but you stopped way short.
所有的婚姻都是强奸
All marriage is rape.
不会吧 这你们也能无声鼓掌
Come on. That gets a weird silent clap?
没错 婚姻制度自有其问题
Yes, marriage is problematic. It is.
但是你们不觉得我们应该避免
But don't you think that we should refrain
把大家的父亲称为强奸犯吗
from just calling everybody's dad a rapist?
我只有一个妈妈 她叫盖亚
I only have one mother, and her name is Gaia.
真有你的 琳达 你厉害
Oh, g-good for you, Linda. That's super.
你们都厉害
Good for all of you.
你们能坐在这儿
It's-- it's wonderful that you get to sit here
在你们的小圈子里
in your little circle with your menstrual blood
把你们的经血涂满你们免费住房的墙壁
smeared all over the walls of your free housing,
在这里争论 跟这栋房子以外的生活
arguing semantics that have nothing to do with life
毫无关系的术语
outside of this building.
-叛徒  -孩子气
- Sellout. - Child!
乘客们请注意
Attention, passengers--
因为机械事故 本该飞往凤凰城的
the inbound flight number 37 from Phoenix is delayed
37号航班有所延误
due to mechanical issues.
今天 明天唤她起床
♪ Today, tomorrow wake her up ♪
看看你周围 你就知道原因
♪ Just look around you, you see the reason why ♪
眼前伪造的一切
♪ The falsification of everything in sight ♪
使你想要逃离 直到我
♪ Made you run around until I... ♪
威士忌不加冰
Maker's neat.
今天 明天唤她起床
♪ Today, tomorrow wake her heart ♪
我不在乎我是死是活
♪ I don't care if I live or die ♪
喷气飞机 大师 节拍
♪ The jet set, the gurus, the beats ♪
看看他们在街上漫步的样子
♪ Look at the way they stroll about the streets ♪
所以你在这里坐了一整天
So you've just been sitting here all day?
对
Yep.
不预约就直奔机场 真有你的风格
Going to the airport without a meeting is so you.
我以为他最后会服输的
I thought he'd fold eventually.
那么没有仙人掌钥匙扣了
So no cactus keychains?
你看到了所有的含义
You see all the implications.
不好说
- Mm-hmm. - I don't know.
当我还小的时候 有个叫吉米·麦戈尔金的男孩
When I was a kid, there was this boy named Jimmy McGurgin.
他开了个买柠檬水的小摊儿
And he opened up a lemonade stand.
是个好生意
It's good business.
可是那家伙不让我入伙
And the punk wouldn't let me in on it.
你知道我怎么做的吗
So you know what I did?
我自己开了个摊儿 但是加了点料
I opened up my own but with a twist.
我加了波旁威士忌 结果在街区大火
I added bourbon to it-- hit of the neighborhood.
当妈的 当爸的 大一点的孩子们 大家都爱喝
Moms, dads, older kids, everybody loved it.
我成了他们的英雄
I was their king.
害得吉米关门大吉
I put Jimmy out of business.
那是我生命中最开心的日子之一
One of the happiest days of my life.
那也太惨了
That's super sad.
我之前总知道如何切入 但现在毫无头绪
There's always an angle. I don't know what is going on.
所以 如果你想对我说 我早就说过的
So, look, if you want to tell me I told you so,
现在你可以说了
now would be the time.
这个杂志就是大麻烦
The magazine's an albatross.
你说得对
Y-you were right.
我不会那么说你的
I'm not gonna do that.
你太可怜了
You're pathetic.
我不会对人落井下石的
And I don't kick a man when he's down.
不管怎样 我们也经历过这种事
Anyway, we've been here before.
现在你更足智多谋 有创造力
Now you get resourceful, creative.
对
Yeah.
你会想明白怎么在这个柠檬水里面加波旁威士忌的
You'll figure out how to add some bourbon to the lemonade.
我们能离开这里吗
Can we get out of here?
天花板上困了只鸟
There's a bird that's been trapped in the ceiling
两个小时了 吵得我很不耐烦
for the last two hours, and it's really bumming me out.
我们要顺道去个地方
We got to make a pit stop.
乔伊斯在伍德布里奇卖杂志
Joyce is moving magazines at Woodbridge.
我后备箱里有好几箱
I got a bunch of boxes in the trunk.
身无分文的大学生 太好了
Broke college kids? Perfect.
对
Yep.
妈的
Shit.
-太好了 你在这儿  -嗨
- Fantastic. You're here. - Hi.
-准备走了吗  -嗯 怎么了 出什么事了
- Ready to go? - Yeah. Why? What's going on?
传承者做得很不错
Um, the pledges did a great job,
但是他们急于把杂志卖出去
but in their zeal to impress,
顺道去了个圣经学习组
they made a pit stop at Bible study
给他们留了一些杂志
and may have left some magazines behind.
导致了抗议
That led to a protest,
结果引来了同性恋解放阵线
which brought up the Gay Liberation Front,
对了 那些同志们超喜欢你的杂志
who, by the way, love your magazine.
-是吗  -那是迪恩·奥利弗
- Oh! - Um, and that's Dean Oliver.
他想解释
He's trying to explain
世人对自由言论的立场
the university's stance on free speech...
-好吧  -这显然
- Oh, all right. - Which obviously
引起了公民自由协会的注意
got the attention of the Civil Liberty Association.
你里面进行的顺利吗 温迪同意了吗
Tell me it went better inside. Is Wendy in?
天哪 温迪
God, Wendy.
-怎么了  -温迪
- What? - Wendy.
嘿 温迪 温迪
Hey! Wendy! Wendy!
怎么样 她们了不起吧 是不是
How'd it go? They're something, aren't they?
那些姑娘害怕了 但是你知道的 对不对
Those girls were terrifying, but you knew that, didn't you?
欢迎成为公众眼中的女性主义者
Welcome to being a feminist in the public's eye.
不好对付吧
Tricky, huh?
显然是这样 不过没关系
Yeah, apparently so. But okay, fine.
这可以是你为《风骚女人》杂志写文章的一个角度
That can be the angle for the piece you do for "Minx."
我也想啊 可是我忘了
Oh, I'd love to, but I forgot
我跟《哈泼斯》杂志签了非同行竞争协议
I have a noncompete clause in my deal with "Harper's."
而你现在才想起来
And you're just remembering that now?
-真是凑巧啊  -不厚道啊 温迪
- That's very convenient. - Not cool, Wendy.
欢迎你们致电我的律师
Well, you're welcome to call my lawyer,
看看能不能解除这个条约
see if we can get a carve-out.
他目前正在波斯塔疗养
He's currently in Positano convalescing,
所以可能一时半会儿接不了电话
so it might take a little while.
祝你好运 姐们儿
Good luck, sister.
我支持你
I'm rooting for you.
对了 我从来没看过你的书
I never read your book, by the way!
-天哪  -老天爷
- Oh, my God! - Jesus Christ.
我还以为他们会喜欢我
I really thought that they would like me.
大学生嘛
College.
现在去派对还很早
Oh, my gosh, we're gonna be early for that party.
在那里 他们动作很快的
Well, in there, they're so fast.
提醒我在帕萨迪纳总是被捕
Remind me to always get arrested in Pasadena.
再说说你要去哪儿
Tell me where you're going again?
你也要来好吧
Oh, you're coming with. Yeah.
艾略特·古德的替身在峡谷搞事情
Elliot Gould's stunt double is blowin' it out in the Canyon.
地狱天使乐队负责安保
Hell's Angels are running security,
不过我以前跟他们巡演经理有一腿 所以我们可以进去
but I used to bang their road captain, so we'll get in.
警察有理由抓你们进去
Did you give those pigs the what-for?
你知道有的
You know we did.
谢丽 这是长腿约翰
Oh, Shelly, this is Long John.
你好 好吧
Oh, hello. Okay.
嗯
Yeah.
有人喜欢广藿香啊
Someone likes patchouli.
-好吧  -嗯
- Okay. - Yeah.
我们走
Let's go.
点火吧
Fire that shit up.
我知道他的眼神有点迷离
I know his eyes are totally saucered,
不过他可是高水平的嗑药司机
but he's an above-average stoned driver.
而且 穆赫兰离这里只有19英里
Also, Mulholland is only, like, 19 miles away,
我们会到的
so we'll get there.
我还是 我先回家吧
I should, uh, probably get home.
什么 不要 面包合唱团的前鼓手也要表演
What? No! Bread's ex-drummer is gonna play,
我听说他嗑药太多所以被踢出乐队了
and I heard he got kicked out 'cause he rocked too hard.
我 我是喜欢面包合唱团的
Oh, I do-- I do love Bread.
只不过这周我们才让米莉从婴儿床搬出来
It's just we just moved Milly out of her crib this week,
我答应过她今晚上在她上床之前
and I promised her I'd do a monster check
我会检查床下有没有怪兽的 说来很傻
under her bed tonight, which is silly,
因为大家都知道怪兽是住在衣柜里的
'cause everyone knows monsters live in the closet.
我们送你去你车子那边
We'll give you a ride to your car.
我 我想走走
Oh, I-- uh, I could use the walk.
我想是这样
I think so.
-嘿  -嗯
- Hey, um... - Yeah.
用一下水网喷雾
Use a can of Aqua Net.
告诉她这个可以吓走怪兽
Tell her it's monster spray.
我妈妈以前就是这么做的
That's what my mom used to do for me.
好的
Okay.
这个杂志不应该出现在我们想要的未来
This magazine should have no place in the future we want!
《风骚女人》会毁掉我们的运动 让我们
"Minx" will destroy our movement before we have a--
-不好意思 让一下  -看着点
- Excuse me. Excuse me. - Watch it!
开始
Here you go.
大家站出来
So step right up
将这个女权主义的冒牌货
and deposit this piece of feminist impostor-ism
扔进垃圾堆
into the trash heap!
下体可耻 下体可耻
Dong is wrong! Dong is wrong!
all: Dong is wrong! Dong is wrong!
-我受够了  -下体可耻
I'm done with this! all: Dong is wrong!
下体可耻
Dong is wrong! Dong is wrong!
把那本《风骚女人》扔进垃圾堆
Throw that "Minx" crap in the trash!
大家一起说 《风骚女人》滚蛋
Let me hear you say it! Down with "Minx"!
《风骚女人》滚蛋
Down with "Minx"!
不知道我们这么做有什么意义
I don't even know why we're doing this!
因为它们是你的杂志
Because they're your magazines.
上面有口水的杂志就不要捡了
Maybe just skip the ones with spit on them.
天哪
Oh, God!
-嘿 站住  -嘿嘿
Hey, stop right-- Hey! Hey!
-《风骚女人》滚蛋  -里根操蛋
all: Down with "Minx"! - Fuck Reagan!
这一点无可辩驳 兄弟
Hard to argue with that, buddy.
混蛋
Prick.
-《风骚女人》滚蛋  -《风骚女人》操蛋
all: Down with "Minx"! - Fuck "Minx"!
《风骚女人》滚蛋
all: Down with "Minx"!
-你能相信这个场面吗  -我信
- Can you believe this shit? - Yeah, I can.
-直说吧  -行吧
- Let it out. - Fine.
我的确告诉过你的
I did tell you so.
从一开始我就说过 这不是个好主意
I told you from the start this was a bad bet.
你迷失了 道格 《风骚女人》很烂
You lost, Doug. "Minx" is a dog.
是啊 现在没有多少喜欢我们的人哈
Yeah, we don't have a lot fans right now, do we?
我已经做了你让我做的一切
I've done everything you've asked.
当我想要尖叫时我一直保持了沉默
I've been silent when I wanted to scream.
当我明知道你不对时还是维护了你
I've defended you when I knew you were guilty.
这一切都为了什么
All in service of what?
一个不知名却极贵的试验吗
An off-brand, very expensive experiment?
如果我们不及时止损
This weird legitimacy thing
这个尚未被合法的东西
that if we don't cut our losses
我们整个公司都会被拖垮的
will burn our whole company to the ground.
《风骚女人》滚蛋
all: Down with "Minx"!
让我说出所有这些话 你真是操蛋
And fuck you for making me have to say all this stuff.
我是圣诞聚会上喝得最多的人
I'm the drunkest person at the Christmas party.
我是最会玩的蒂娜
I'm Good Time Tina!
嘿 妹子
Hey, girl.
没跟你说话 继续骑车 小屁孩
Not you. Eh, keep riding, junior.
《风骚女人》滚蛋
all: Down with "Minx"!
好吧 是谁扔了精装版的圣经
All right, who throws a hardback Bible?
-还在流血吗  -嗯
- Is it still bleeding? - Yes, yes.
我真是 我感觉这是我的责任
I'm so s-- I-I-I feel responsible.
是我 我应该为此负责吗
Am I-- am I-- am I responsible?
你说的是法律上还是道德上
Are you talking legally or morally?
不知道 可能两者都有吧
I don't know. Both, I guess.
也许我们可以问问温迪的律师
Maybe we could ask Wendy's lawyer.
告诉我这一切都会结束的
Just tell me that this is all gonna blow over.
会没事的 好吧
It'll be fine, okay?
我知道这感觉就像世界末日
I know it seems like the end of the world,
一群大学生互相吼来吼去
a bunch of college kids yelling at each other,
可是这种事天天都有发生
but it happens every day.
耶 篝火
Yeah, bonfire!
整个晚上 我爱着她
♪ All night long, I loved her ♪
清晨来得太早
♪ Morning came too soon ♪
我早知道下午她就会离开
♪ I knew she'd be gone by the afternoon ♪
我说 拜托别走
♪ I said, "Please don't go" ♪
她还是说了再见
♪ Still she said goodbye ♪
但是当她转过头来 她眼里那种眼神
♪ But as she turned around, she got a Iook in her eye ♪
当她转过头来 她眼里那种眼神
♪ As she turned around, she got a look in her eye ♪
我觉得那表示
♪ And I thought it said ♪
当你环顾四周来找我
♪ When you look round to see me ♪
在你床上转过身来
♪ Turn around in your bed ♪
我的体温会温暖你
♪ The warmth of my body will heat you ♪
让你感觉热血沸腾
♪ Make your blood run cherry red ♪
热血沸腾
♪ Cherry red ♪